{
    "question": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old english term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".    2. IBM is has laid of 20 percent of their workforce with a signature on a single piece of paper.\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6\r\na. Find out the error option.\r\nb. Explain why it is wrong\r\n\r\nmohon bantuannya yaa..",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old English term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".<br>Positive Meaning : It&#039;s a person that we concern as lovely and lovable, therefore we prioritize this darling as the first priority.<br>Negative : Since the word darling means favorite minion, it also trigger the feeling of possessiveness, that sometime it has negative effect on their freedom and privacy.\u00a0<br><br><span>2.\u00a0</span><u>IBM</u><span>\u00a0is\u00a0</span><u>has</u><span>\u00a0laid of\u00a0</span><u>20 percent</u><span>\u00a0of\u00a0</span><u>their</u>\u00a0<u>workforce</u><span>\u00a0with a signature on a\u00a0</span><u>single</u><span>\u00a0piece of paper.</span><br>\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6<br>a. Find out the error option.<br><br>number 2 - &gt; should be<br>IBM has laid without &#039;is&#039;\u00a0<br>b. Explain why it is wrong<br>if we use Is, then it will have pasive meaning, which means that IBM get bankrupt due to their worker\u00a0<br><br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-gak-cara-menjawab-soal-bahasa-inggris-un-sma-dengan-902",
            "question": "Ada yang tau gak cara menjawab soal Bahasa Inggris UN SMA dengan trik tertentu supaya cepat dalam mengerjakannya.?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalau mau mengerjakan soal bhs inggris dengan mudah ya kalu bisa tau artinya soal bhs inggris itu pasti tau jawabanya.....<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Perbanyak vocabulary, sering-sering ngelakuin latihan listening karena 20 soal pertama di UN SMA ngegunain metode ini. Perbanyak baca modul buat ngebantu. Ngulang soal yang sudah dikerjain. Dan terakhir do&#039;a minta kemudahan",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-perbedaan-antara-simple-past-tense-dengan-present-perfect-ten-100",
            "question": "Apa perbedaan antara simple past tense dengan present perfect tense ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple pastanse untuk menyatakan kejadian yang sudah lalu<br>present perfect untuk menyatakan kejadian yang direncanakan",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "simple past tense dipakai saat keterangan waktunya sudah selesai, \nsedangkan present perfect dipakai saat keterangan waktunya belum \nselesai/masih berlanjut.<br>Contoh:<br>I bought 3 books last week. (simple past-last week sudah berlalu)<br>I have bought 3 books this week. (present perfect-this week belum berlalu, masih berlangsung)<br><br>present perfect menggunakan &#039;for&#039; dan &#039;since&#039; saat kegiatannya masih berlanjut.<br><br>I have lived in London for 3 years. (present perfect-masih berlangsung, sekarang pun masih di London)<br>I have lived in London since 1990. (sampai sekarang masih tinggal di London)\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "choose-inappropriate-structure-in-the-following-sentences-or-dial-968",
            "question": "choose inappropriate structure in the following sentences or dialog below ! man : how's your new job at the hospital ? \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 A woman : it's great and my co-workers sre so nice \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 C man : good. that's important for you to feel exciting with your workers \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0D",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>man : good. that&#039;s important for you to feel <u>exciting</u> with your workers</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatin-sinopsis-film-cloudy-a-chance-of-meatballs-2-dong-pake-bhs-151",
            "question": "buatin sinopsis film cloudy a chance of meatballs 2 dong pake bhs indonesia gpp..nanti aku yang translate sendiri...tolong bantu ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "It&#039;s always been Flint&#039;s dream \nto be recognized as a great inventor, but everything changes when he \ndiscovers that his most infamous machine (which turns water into food) \nis still operating and is now creating food-animal hybrids - \n\"foodimals!\" With the fate of humanity in his hands, Chester sends Flint\n and his friends on a dangerously delicious mission - to battle hungry \ntacodiles, shrimpanzees, hippotatomuses, cheespiders and other food \ncreatures to save the world again!            \n                <span>- <span>Written by\nColumbia Pictures</span></span>        \n            <span>\nFlint Lockwood is a genius who created a machine that turns water into \nfood which went out of control. Flint would stop it. He would set out to\n build his own lab with Sam Sparks. But Chester V, the scientist who \ninspired Flint comes to the island to clean up the mess, the machine \nmade, and offers Flint a job at his lab. Flint takes it. Later, Dr. V \ntells him that the machine is now creating living food\n and they could be a threat. So he goes back to the island along with \nhis friends including Sam to stop it. But Sam tells flint that they \ncould acting hastily but Dr. V convinces Flint otherwise. So they leave \nFlint and eventually learn the truth.            </span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-the-jumbled-words-to-form-meaningful-sentencesstarting-w-193",
            "question": "arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words. 1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place 2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a \u00a0 mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "2. Mr. Kukuh and his family will go to Bali and Lombok if they have a long holiday this year<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggris-dia-mengernyitkan-alisnya-547",
            "question": "Apa bahasa Inggris dia mengernyitkan alisnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "he furrowed his brow",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bagaima-membalas-surat-kepada-pembeli-tersebut-kiara-agusta-jal-156",
            "question": "Bagaima membalas surat kepada pembeli tersebut??    kiara agusta\r\njalan W.Z Johanes No. 621\r\nThe Tiny Tots Toy Company\r\nJalan Kuningan Sari No. 50, Jakarta\r\nDear Costumer Service Respresentative,\r\n\r\nI recently purchased one of your Tiny Tents (Model #47485) for my three-year old daughter. Unfortunately, after viewing the components that came with the product, I discovered that four of the parts were missing. Also, the instructions that came with the tent are in portuguese and Russian, but not in english or french, the two languages I speak. These two unforeseen problems have resulted in the tent remeaning unassembled and unacceptable as a toy my daughter.\r\nI am writing to request replacements for the missing parts, and a copy of the full set of assembly instructions (in english or french) for the model I purchased. If reasonable arrangements are not made within ten bussines days, I will return the tent to the store I purchased it from and expect a full refund. To assist you in processing my request, I am including a copy of my sales receipt and a list of the missing parts.\r\nI have purchased other toys manufactured by your company in the past, and have always been impressed with the quality and selection that Tiny Tots has made available to its customers. I sincerely hope this is a one-time incident, and that any future purchases I make will live up to the standard my family has come to expect from your company.\r\n\r\nSincerely,\r\nKiara Agusta",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dear Kiara Agusta,<br><br>I am glad that you let us know about this matter. We are more than happy to assist you and would like to keep you impress with our service. We apologize for the missing part of the screw which supposed to be attached to the tents. We will send it tomorrow. And also the copy of the instruction will be delivered together with these missing parts. Hopefully you are satisfied with our reply and always be our loyal customer<br><br>Regards<br><br>Toytots Representative<br>Laura <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-407",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "rumahku yg indah. bercat merah muda,di depannya dibuat pagar, di dalam terdiri dari ruang tamu,ruang keluarga,2 kamar mandi,2 tempat tidur. di belakang ada taman dipenuhi bunga bunga yg sangat indah dan ayunan <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dari-dialog-bergaining-987",
            "question": "Contoh dari dialog bergaining?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "In a traditional market there are two friends named Rifky and Obet. They are looking for goldfish, they are going to make a party at Rifky\u2019s house by roasting goldfish.<br><span>Rifky:\u00a0we should buy cheaper goldfish because our money is not much<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0sure, that\u2019s why we have to round to get the cheaper price<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0but I\u2019m tired..we have rounded the whole part of this market but the price of all goldfish is almost the same<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0Look at there\u2026! There\u2019s a goldfish Fishmonger that we have not been there yet<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0ok, come on<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0what the price of this goldfish in a kilo?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0It\u2019s 27.000 rupiahs a kilo<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0That\u2019s too expensive,\u00a0\u00a0may I bargain?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0How much can you pay, boys?<br></span><span>Obet: what about 20.000 rupiahs a kilo?<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0sorry I can\u2019t. it\u2019s a local goldfish, taken from ponds around this area<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0\u00a0give me a break\u2026you must decrease the price. You said that we may bargain.<br></span><span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I&#039;ll make a special price for you, boys.</span>\u00a025.000 rupiahs a kilo. What about that?<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0I don\u2019t think so, give me 22.000 rupiahs a kilo and we\u2019ll take 3 kilos<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I\u2019m loss..I have no profit if I sell with that price. Just for you boys I give you 22.500 rupiahs per kilo but you have to buy 4 kilos. Do you agree?<br></span><span>Rifky:give us for second please.<br></span>RIFKY WISPERING OBET<br><span>Rifky: \u00a0 it\u2019s cheaper among all the goldfish Fishmonger that we have visited. Should we take it?<br></span><span>Obet: yes I know\u2026ok we just take it<br></span><span>Rifky: Ok, we\u2019ll take 4 kilos for 22.500 rupiahs<br></span><span>Fishmonger: that\u2019s a wise buyer\u2026here\u2019s the fish boy. I hope you feel satisfied.<br></span><span>Rifky and Obet: thank you</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-to-a-good-sentences-1-realized-i-just-mistakes-919",
            "question": "Arrange to a good sentences !    1)\u00a0realized - I - just - mistakes - had - we - made -\r\n2) they - when - gone - arrived - had - we - already\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Maaf saya hanya bisa menyusun yang nomor 2, semoga membantu ya :)<br>2) We had already arrived when they gone.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. \"I realized mistakes we had made\" (saya menyadari kesalahan-kesalahan yang telah kita buat), or \"I realized we had made mistakes\" (saya menyadari bahwa kita telah melakukan kesalahan-kesalahan).<br>2. \"They had already gone when we arrived\" (mereka telah pergi ketika kita tiba), or \"We had alredy gone when they arrived\" (kita telah pergi ketika mereka tiba).<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}